http://www.ncfi.com/privacy-policy/

Applications
Flexible »
Bedding
Furniture
Transportation
Marine
See all »
Insulation »
Residential Insulation
Commercial Insulation
Architects
Roofing »
Residential Roofing
Commercial Roofing
Roofing Professionals
Geotechnical »
See All
Custom »
Rigid Molding
See all »
Products
Flexible »
Stat-Guard
Insulation »
AgriThane™
Roofing »
Enduratech Products
Geotechnical »
Terrathane Products
Custom »
OEM Solutions
Equipment »
Find Your Account Manager
Technical Library »
Find an Applicator »
Health & Safety »
Latest News »
Contact Us »
Collection and Use of Information
We will collect personally identifiable information you provide to us directly or through a web site, including but not limited to your name, job title, employer’s name, address, telephone numbers, fax numbers, and e-mail address. BMC may use and store such information to notify you of official business, provide a product or sample you requested, evaluate prospective customer needs and interests, and alert you of BMC news, activities, services and benefits. Personally identifiable information will be collected only for the purposes of completing a MSDS and/or sample request, or submitting information for a newsletter, white paper or other item. BMC reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics to measure interest in and use of the various areas of its Web site. The user may withdraw consent of BMC collection and maintenance of user information and to receipt of communications from us. The process to withdraw consent requires written notification to BMC at info@barnhardt.net. We will acknowledge the request then remove all data retained on the user.
The network of Web Sites (collectively, the “Barnhardt Manufacturing Company Web Sites”) operated by the Barnhardt Manufacturing Company (BMC) or its affiliates or subsidiaries (“Intrinsics”, “Richmond Dental”, “NCFI”, etc.), is comprised of various Web sites and Web pages. The BMC Web Sites are offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein. Your use of the BMC Web Sites constitutes your agreement to all such terms, conditions, and notices. Your use of a particular BMC website included within the BMC Web Sites network may also be subject to additional terms outlined elsewhere on that website (the “Additional Terms”). Additionally, the BMC Web Sites may themselves contain additional terms that govern particular features or offers (for example, sweepstakes or chat areas). In the event that any of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein conflict with the Additional Terms or other terms and guidelines contained within any particular BMC website, then these terms shall control.
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS OF USE AND DISCLAIMERS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEB SITE (this “Site”). By accessing or using this Site, you agree to these terms of use, conditions and all applicable laws. If you do not agree to these terms you may not use this Site.
Modification of these Terms of Use
Unless otherwise specified, the BMC Web Sites are for your personal and noncommercial use. You may not modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, software, products or services obtained from the BMC Web Sites.
You may display and, subject to any expressly stated restrictions or limitations relating to specific material, electronically copy, download and print hard copy portions of the material from the different areas of the Site solely for your own noncommercial use, or to place an order with BMC or to purchase BMC products. Any other use of materials on this Site, including but not limited to the modification, reproduction, distribution, republication, display or transmission of the content of this Site, without prior written permission of BMC is strictly prohibited.
Harassment in any manner or form on the Site or any of the BMC Websites, including via e-mail and chat or by obscene or abusive language is strictly forbidden. Impersonation of others, including a BMC employee, host, or representative or other members or visitors on the Site is prohibited. You may not upload to, distribute, or otherwise publish through the Site any content which is libelous, defamatory, obscene, threatening, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, abusive, illegal, or otherwise objectionable, or which may constitute or encourage a criminal offense, violate the rights of any party or otherwise give rise to liability or violate any law. You may not upload commercial content on the Site or use the Site to solicit others to join or become members of any other commercial online service or other organization.
We currently use Google Analytics, Google AdWords Conversion tracker, and other Google services that place cookies on a browser across the website. These cookies help us increase the website’s effectiveness for our visitors. These cookies are set and read by Google. To learn more and/or opt out of Google tracking, please visit this page.
We use AdWords remarketing to market our sites across the web. We place a cookie on a browser, and then a 3rd party (Google) reads these cookies and may serve an ad on a 3rd party site. You may opt out of this ad serving on Google’s opt out page.
Copyrights and Trademarks
The entire content included in this Site, including but not limited to text, design, graphics, interfaces, or code and the selection and arrangements thereof is copyrighted as a collective work under the United States and other copyright laws, and is the property of BMC. The collective work includes works that are licensed to BMC. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. All trademarks, service marks, and trade names (collectively the “Marks”) are trademarks or registered trademarks of and are proprietary to Barnhardt Manufacturing Company, or other respective owners that have granted BMC the right and license to use such Marks.
Typographical Errors
In the event a BMC product or service is listed at an incorrect price due to typographical error or error in pricing information received from our suppliers, BMC shall have the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for product or service listed at the incorrect price. BMC shall have the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is canceled, BMC shall issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the incorrect price.
User Participation
BMC does not and cannot review all communications and materials posted to or created by users accessing the Site and is not in any manner responsible for the content of these communications and materials. You acknowledge that by providing you with the ability to view and distribute user generated content on the Site, BMC is merely acting as a passive conduit for such distribution and is not undertaking any obligation or liability relating to any contents or activities on the Site. However, BMC reserves the right to block or remove communications or materials that it determines to be (a) abusive, defamatory, or obscene, (b) fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading, (c) in violation of a copyright, trademark or; other intellectual property right of another or (d) violates any law or regulation or (e) offensive or otherwise unacceptable to BMC at its sole discretion. Note that any personally identifiable information you may post or transmit will be treated by BMC in accordance with BMC’s Privacy Statement.
User Submissions
Except for any personally identifiable information we may collect from you under the guidelines established in our Privacy Statement, any material, information or other communication you transmit, upload or post to this Site (“Communications”) will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. BMC will have no obligations with respect to the Communications. BMC and its designees will be free to copy, disclose, distribute, incorporate and otherwise use the Communications and all data, images, sounds, text, and other things embodied therein for any and all commercial or noncommercial purposes.
User Chat Rooms
BMC may, but is not obligated to, monitor or review any areas on the Site where users transmit or post Communications or communicate solely with each other, including but not limited to chat rooms, bulletin boards or other user forums, and the content of any such Communications. BMC, however, will have no liability related to the content of any such Communications, whether or not arising under the laws of copyright, trademarks, libel, privacy, obscenity, or otherwise.
Third-Party Links
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, this Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third party vendors and other third parties (the “External Sites”). However, even if the third party is affiliated with BMC, BMC has no control over these linked sites, all of which have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of BMC. BMC has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk. Links do not imply that BMC sponsors, endorses, is affiliated with or associated with, or has been legally authorized to use any trademark, trade name, service mark, design, logo, symbol or other copyrighted materials displayed on or accessible through such External Sites. Nonetheless, BMC seeks to protect the integrity of its Site and the links placed upon it and therefore requests any feedback on not only its own Site, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work). You should contact the Site administrator or Webmaster for those External Sites if you have any concerns regarding such links or the content located on such External Sites.
Disclaimer
The Barnhardt Manufacturing Company makes no warranties or representations about the accuracy or completeness of this Site’s content or the content of any site or External Sites.
The Barnhardt Manufacturing Company does not filter advertisements or other content that children may view through our sites or “hot-linked” sites, and they could receive content and materials from the Internet and/or advertising that are inappropriate for children. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to consider using an electronic filtering software.
THIS SITE AND THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION, SERVICES, AND PRODUCTS IN THIS SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TEXT, GRAPHICS, AND LINKS, ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, BMC DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUS, AND WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR COURSE OF PERFORMANCE. BMC DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SITE AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. BMC DOES NOT MAKE ANY WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OF THE MATERIALS IN THIS SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR COMPLETENESS, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, USEFULNESS, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY OR OTHERWISE. THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL BMC BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL, DAMAGES, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, EVEN IF BMC HAS BEEN PREVIOUSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, OR ANY OTHER THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, OR PERFORMANCE OF THE INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, AND MATERIALS AVAILABLE FROM THIS SITE. THESE LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY NOTWITHSTANDING ANY FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY LIMITED REMEDY. BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless BMC, its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers (collectively the “Provider”) from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, resulting from any violation of these terms and conditions or any activity related to your Internet account (including negligent or wrongful conduct), by you or any other person accessing the Site using your Internet account.
Applicable Laws
Your use of this Site shall be governed in all respects by the laws of the state of North Carolina, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law provisions, and not by the 1980 U.N. Convention on contracts for the international sale of goods. You agree that jurisdiction over and venue in any legal proceeding directly or indirectly arising out of or relating to this Site (including but not limited to the purchase of BMC products) shall be in the state or federal courts located in North Carolina. Any cause of action or claim you may have with respect to the Site (including but not limited to the purchase of BMC products) must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. BMC’s failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of these terms and conditions shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Neither the course of conduct between the parties nor trade practice shall act to modify any of these terms and conditions. BMC may assign its rights and duties under this Agreement to any party at any time without notice to you.
BMC makes no representation that materials in the Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to them from territories where their content is illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this Site from locations outside North Carolina do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. You may not use or export the materials in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations. Any claim relating to the materials shall be governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of North Carolina.
General
BMC may revise these Terms at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then-current Terms because they are binding on you. Certain provisions of these Terms may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages at this Site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
